['The', 'French', 'Anti-Doping', 'agency', '(', 'AFLD', ')', 'on', 'Thursday', 'adjourned', 'its', 'hearing', 'into', 'the', 'doping', 'case', 'against', 'Tour', 'de', 'France', 'winner', 'Floyd', 'Landis', '.']
['O', 'NATIONALITY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']
Floyd nn France
['Embattled', 'Bush', 'to', 'veto', 'Iraq', 'deadline']
['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O']
Bush xcomp Iraq
['Key', 'US', 'Senate', 'panel', 'approves', 'Petraeus', 'to', 'head', 'US', 'forces', 'in', 'Iraq']
['O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY']
Petraeus xcomp US
['New', 'Zealand', 'cricket', 'boss', 'Martin', 'Sneddon', 'started', 'the', 'ball', 'rolling', 'at', 'the', 'post', '-', 'match', 'ceremony', '.']
['COUNTRY', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Martin nn Zealand
['Taiwan', "'s", 'ex-president', 'Lee', 'may', 'visit', 'Japan', ':', 'report']
['COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O']
Lee rcmod Japan
['US', 'House', 'condemns', 'Bush', 'Iraq', 'strategy']
['LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'COUNTRY', 'O']
Bush iobj Iraq
['Football', ':', "'", 'Asian', 'Maradona', "'", 'hails', 'Iran', 'fightback']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'NATIONALITY', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O']
Maradona rcmod Iran
['Football', ':', 'Man', 'City', 'boss', 'Pearce', 'delighted', 'with', 'Barton', 'pledge']
['O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O']
Pearce nn City
['Joining', 'Kerr', 'and', 'Sharp', 'in', 'sixth', 'place', 'were', 'Sweden', "'s", 'Maria', 'Hjorth', 'and', 'Australian', "'s", 'Rachel', 'Hetherington', '.']
['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'NATIONALITY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']
Kerr aux Sweden
['Jaish', 'was', 'banned', 'by', 'key', 'US', 'ally', 'President', 'Pervez', 'Musharraf', 'in', '2002', '.']
['PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'DATE', 'O']
Musharraf amod US
['Smith', ',', 'originally', 'named', 'the', 'Africa', 'captain', ',', 'was', 'replaced', 'with', 'his', 'South', 'Africa', 'team-mate', 'Mark', 'Boucher', 'after', 'undergoing', 'knee', 'surgery', 'last', 'month', '.']
['PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CAUSE_OF_DEATH', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O']
Mark nn Africa
['Smith', ',', 'originally', 'named', 'the', 'Africa', 'captain', ',', 'was', 'replaced', 'with', 'his', 'South', 'Africa', 'team-mate', 'Mark', 'Boucher', 'after', 'undergoing', 'knee', 'surgery', 'last', 'month', '.']
['PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CAUSE_OF_DEATH', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O']
Mark poss South
['-', 'West', 'Indies', 'captain', 'Brian', 'Lara', '.']
['O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']
Brian nn Indies
['The', 'most', 'important', 'thing', 'is', 'getting', 'England', 'back', 'on', 'track', ',', '"', 'said', 'Vaughan', '.']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O']
Vaughan ccomp England
['Cricket', ':', 'Ton-up', 'Tendulkar', 'leads', 'India', 'run', 'feast']
['O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O']
Tendulkar rcmod India
['Earlier', 'this', 'year', 'US', 'magnates', 'George', 'Gillett', 'and', 'Tom', 'Hicks', 'bought', 'Liverpool', 'for', '438', 'million', 'pounds', '.']
['DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'O']
George dep US
['URGENT', 'Denmark', "'s", 'Tour', 'de', 'France', 'winner', 'Riis', 'admits', 'to', 'doping']
['O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Riis nn France
['-', 'New', 'Zealand', 'captain', 'Stephen', 'Fleming']
['O', 'COUNTRY', 'COUNTRY', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']
Stephen nn Zealand
['Only', 'Russia', "'s", 'foreign', 'minister', ',', 'Sergei', 'Lavrov', ',', 'defended', 'Lukashenko', ',', 'saying', 'the', 'protest', 'had', 'not', 'been', 'authorised', '"', 'as', 'is', 'required', 'under', 'the', 'law', '.', '"']
['O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'TITLE', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Lukashenko advmod Russia
['On', 'Thursday', ',', 'Fatah', "'s", 'one-time', 'Gaza', 'strongman', 'Mohammed', 'Dahlan', 'formally', 'resigned', 'as', 'national', 'security', 'adviser', 'at', 'the', 'request', 'of', 'the', 'commission', '.']
['O', 'DATE', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Mohammed amod Gaza
["'", 'We', 'love', 'Assad', "'", 'posters', 'fill', 'Syria', 'for', 'no-contest', 'vote', 'by', 'Roueida', 'Mabardi']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']
Assad ccomp Syria
['URGENT', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', 'Talabani', 'says', 'Iraq', 'could', 'extradite', 'rebels', ':', 'Turkish', 'govt', 'source']
['O', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NATIONALITY', 'O', 'O']
Talabani rcmod Iraq
['Northern', 'Ireland', 'manager', 'Nigel', 'Worthington', 'admits', 'he', 'is', 'unsure', 'of', 'his', 'future', 'after', 'his', 'side', "'s", 'heroic', 'effort', 'to', 'reach', 'Euro', '2008', 'ended', 'in', 'failure', '.']
['LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Nigel amod Ireland
['His', 'US', 'counterpart', 'Zalmay', 'Khalilzad', 'however', 'noted', 'that', 'although', 'Russia', 'was', 'also', 'a', 'member', 'of', 'the', 'Contact', 'Group', ',', 'it', 'had', 'no', 'right', 'of', 'veto', 'in', 'the', 'process', '.']
['O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Zalmay poss US
['It', 'was', "n't", 'always', 'a', 'pretty', 'sight', 'and', ',', 'not', 'for', 'the', 'first', 'time', ',', 'Australia', 'great', 'David', 'Campese', 'slammed', 'England', 'for', 'their', '"', 'boring', '"', 'rugby', '.']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
David ccomp England
['US', 'Attorney', 'General', 'Gonzales', 'visits', 'Iraq']
['LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY']
Gonzales dep Iraq
['US', 'says', 'Ramadan', 'could', 'decide', 'Iraq', 'troop', 'cut']
['LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O']
Ramadan ccomp Iraq
['Justine', 'Caines', ',', 'whose', 'new', 'political', 'party', 'What', 'Women', 'Want', 'debuted', 'at', 'Saturday', "'s", 'election', ',', 'also', 'welcomed', 'Gillard', "'s", 'new', 'status', 'but', 'said', 'Australia', "'s", 'major', 'parties', 'had', 'traditionally', 'been', 'unkind', 'to', 'women', '.']
['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Gillard conj_but Australia
['"', 'What', 'caused', 'Sharon', 'to', 'leave', 'Gaza', ',', 'Barak', 'to', 'leave', 'Lebanon', 'in', '2000', '?', '"']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O']
Sharon xcomp Gaza
['Others', 'present', 'from', 'the', 'league', 'champions', 'were', 'former', 'Seville', 'stars', 'Sergio', 'Ramos', ',', 'Javier', 'Saviola', 'and', 'Brazilian', 'Julio', 'Baptista', '.']
['O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'NATIONALITY', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']
Sergio amod Seville
['URGENT', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', 'US', 'backs', 'Strauss-Kahn', 'for', 'top', 'IMF', 'post']
['O', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O']
Strauss-Kahn num US
['Successor', 'named', 'to', 'veteran', 'N.', 'Ireland', 'leader', 'Paisley']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'PERSON']
Paisley amod N.
['Successor', 'named', 'to', 'veteran', 'N.', 'Ireland', 'leader', 'Paisley']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'PERSON']
Paisley nn Ireland
['After', 'the', 'Cole', 'bombing', 'that', 'killed', '17', 'US', 'sailors', 'Badawi', 'was', 'featured', 'on', 'a', 'US', 'list', 'of', 'most-wanted', 'terrorists', 'with', 'a', 'five', '-', 'million-dollar', 'bounty', 'on', 'his', 'head', '.']
['O', 'O', 'MISC', 'CRIMINAL_CHARGE', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Badawi num US
['Abbas', 'urges', 'Obama', 'to', 'make', 'Mideast', 'peace', 'a', 'priority']
['PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Obama xcomp Mideast
['The', 'BBC', 'quoted', 'Assad', 'as', 'saying', 'Syria', 'reserved', 'the', 'right', 'to', 'respond', 'to', 'the', 'attack', '.']
['O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CAUSE_OF_DEATH', 'O']
Assad prepc_as Syria
['URGENT', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', 'US', 'envoy', 'Hill', 'to', 'meet', 'NKorean', 'counterpart']
['O', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O']
Hill num US
['US', 'envoy', 'warns', 'Bush', 'is', 'pushing', 'Turkey', ',', 'Iran', 'together']
['LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O']
Bush ccomp Turkey
['We', 'go', 'out', 'with', 'our', 'heads', 'held', 'high', ',', '"', 'said', 'the', 'Northern', 'Ireland', 'manager', 'Nigel', 'Worthington', '.']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']
Nigel det Northern
['We', 'go', 'out', 'with', 'our', 'heads', 'held', 'high', ',', '"', 'said', 'the', 'Northern', 'Ireland', 'manager', 'Nigel', 'Worthington', '.']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']
Nigel amod Ireland
['Athletics', ':', 'Recalled', 'Koech', 'joins', 'Kenya', "'s", 'Olympic', 'squad']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'MISC', 'O']
Koech ccomp Kenya
['Defiant', 'Merkel', 'urges', 'China', 'to', 'talk', 'to', 'Dalai', 'Lama', ':', 'report']
['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Merkel rcmod China
['"', 'I', 'do', "n't", 'think', 'Australia', 'is', 'interested', ',', '"', 'said', 'Jones', '.']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O']
Jones ccomp Australia
['former', 'US', 'attorney', 'general', 'Ramsey', 'Clark', 'told', 'reporters', 'last', 'month', '.']
['O', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O']
Clark amod US
['At', 'the', 'Shanghai', 'competition', ',', 'Powell', 'complained', 'that', 'he', 'was', '"', 'not', 'allowed', '"', 'to', 'face', 'arch-rival', 'US', 'sprinter', 'Tyson', 'Gay', 'in', 'a', 'rematch', 'of', 'their', 'world', 'championship', 'final', '.']
['O', 'O', 'CITY', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Tyson amod US
['Democrats', 'prod', 'Bush', 'to', 'tighten', 'US', 'Pakistan', 'strategy']
['IDEOLOGY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O']
Bush xcomp US
['Tennis', ':', 'Ailing', 'opponent', 'irritates', 'Pennetta', 'in', 'testing', 'Bali', 'victory']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O']
Pennetta prep_in Bali
['Steinmeier', 'met', 'with', 'visiting', 'UN', 'chief', 'Ban', 'Ki-moon', 'Tuesday', 'and', 'called', 'Lavrov', 'and', 'US', 'Secretary', 'of', 'State', 'Condoleezza', 'Rice', 'this', 'week', 'to', 'discuss', 'Abkhazia', '.']
['PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'TITLE', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'TITLE', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O']
Lavrov xcomp Abkhazia
['URGENT', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', '\xc2\xa5', 'Film', 'maker', 'Spielberg', 'boycotts', 'China', 'Olympics', 'over', 'Darfur']
['O', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'MISC', 'O', 'LOCATION']
Spielberg dep China
['A', 'team', 'led', 'by', 'Howard', 'Hughes', 'Medical', 'Institute', 'investigator', 'Christopher', 'Walsh', 'visited', 'Turkey', ',', 'Dubai', ',', 'Kuwait', 'and', 'Saudi', 'Arabia', 'to', 'confirm', 'the', 'diagnoses', ',', 'researchers', 'said', '.']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'CITY', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Christopher rcmod Turkey
['RugbyU', ':', 'All', 'Blacks', 'recall', 'Smith', 'to', 'face', 'England']
['O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY']
Smith xcomp England
['The', 'two', 'foreign', 'ministers', 'signed', 'a', 'treaty', 'on', 'avoiding', 'double', 'taxation', ',', 'with', 'Komura', 'thanking', 'Smith', 'for', 'visiting', 'Japan', 'so', 'early', 'in', 'the', 'two-month-old', 'government', "'s", 'tenure', '.']
['O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Smith prepc_for Japan
['British', 'PM', 'backs', 'Zimbabwe', 'arms', 'embargo', ',', 'condemns', 'Mugabe']
['NATIONALITY', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON']
Mugabe nsubj Zimbabwe
['They', 'chose', 'China', 'first', ',', '"', 'said', 'Lee', 'Joong-Hoon', ',', 'head', 'of', 'the', 'Korean', 'Association', 'of', 'India', '.']
['O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O']
Lee ccomp China
['But', 'they', 'then', 'struggled', 'to', 'get', 'out', 'of', 'their', 'own', '22', 'as', 'Saracens', ',', 'with', 'veteran', 'England', 'back-row', 'Richard', 'Hill', 'involved', ',', 'attacked', 'at', 'a', 'ferocious', 'pace', '.']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Richard amod England
['-', 'April', '12', ':', 'Chinese', 'President', 'Hu', 'Jintao', 'meets', 'Taiwan', "'s", 'vice', 'president-elect', 'Vincent', 'Siew', 'on', 'the', 'Chinese', 'island', 'of', 'Hainan', '.']
['O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'NATIONALITY', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'NATIONALITY', 'O', 'O', 'STATE_OR_PROVINCE', 'O']
Hu rcmod Taiwan
['With', 'no', 'love', 'lost', 'between', 'Chavez', 'and', 'Uribe', ',', 'Chavez', 'slammed', 'Uribe', 'for', 'violating', 'Ecuador', "'s", 'territorial', 'integrity']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Uribe prepc_for Ecuador
['Democratic', 'Republic', 'of', 'Congo', 'troops', 'entered', 'Mushake', ',', 'a', 'strategic', 'eastern', 'village', ',', 'on', 'Tuesday', 'after', 'a', 'second', 'day', 'of', 'heavy', 'clashes', 'with', 'rebel', 'soldiers', ',', 'officers', 'said', '.']
['LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Mushake nsubj of
['With', 'a', '2-1', 'overnight', 'advantage', 'victory', 'was', 'assured', 'when', 'Romania', "'s", 'Victor', 'Hanescu', 'defeated', 'Prakash', 'Amritraj', ',', '6-2', ',', '6-3', ',', '6-1', '.']
['O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'TIME', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O']
Prakash advmod Romania
['Cuba', 'hails', 'Obama', 'win', ',', 'hopes', 'US', 'embargo', 'will', 'ease']
['COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Obama dep US
['German', 'Foreign', 'Minister', 'Frank', 'Walter', 'Steinmeier', 'has', 'called', 'his', 'US', 'counterpart', 'Condoleezza', 'Rice', 'to', 'discuss', 'the', 'case', ',', 'the', 'spokesman', 'said', '.']
['NATIONALITY', 'O', 'TITLE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']
Condoleezza poss US
['Olympics', ':', 'Merritt', 'stuns', 'Wariner', 'to', 'lead', 'US', '400m', 'medal', 'sweep', 'by', 'Jim', 'Slater']
['O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']
Wariner xcomp US
['Britain', 'urges', 'Arab', 'leaders', 'to', 'pressure', 'Iran']
['COUNTRY', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY']
Arab xcomp Iran
['Olympics', ':', 'Birthday', 'girl', 'Wang', 'helps', 'China', 'claim', 'third', 'dive', 'gold']
['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O']
Wang rcmod China
['The', 'Lebanese', 'army', 'was', 'split', 'at', 'the', 'time', ',', 'with', 'most', 'supporting', 'Aoun', 'and', 'the', 'rest', 'Syria', '.']
['O', 'NATIONALITY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'COUNTRY', 'O']
Aoun dobj Syria
